PARADE, THEY RAISE MONEY FOR
COMMUNITY CENTRE 55'S SHARE A
CHRISTMAS PROGRAM.
LOTS OF SANTA CLAUS PARADES
GOING ON.
GREY CUP IS GOING ON AND Z YOU
HEARD IN SPORTS IT'S SNOWING IN
OTTAWA.
THIS IS A SMALL AREA OF LOW
PRESSURE SYSTEM THAT IS SINKING
ACROSS SOUTHEASTERN ONTARIO.
THE DARKER THE BLUE, THE MORE
INTENSE THE SNOW AND THEY'RE
INTO THE MOST INTENSE PART NOW
IN OTTAWA.
IT'S ONLY GOING TO TAPER OFF
FROM THIS POINT FORWARD.
IT'S UP TO 5 CENTIMETRES OF
SNOW.
THE BACK END OF IT IS BRINGING
FLURRIES ACROSS LAKE SIMCOE.
SOME OF THE FLURRIES JUST
STARTING TO EDGE INTO NORTHERN
YORK REGION OVER THE NEXT HOUR
OR TWO.
POSSIBLY UNIONVILLE, MARKHAM AND
NORTHERN AJAX AND WHITBY MAY BE
FLURRIES BEFORE THIS EVENING IS
OUT.
OTHER WISE WE ARE NOT EXPECTING
ACCUMULATION
BY THE WAY, FUTURE CAST,
NOTHING.
I GOT NOTHING.
I GOT A LITTLE BIT OF CLOUD TO
SHOW YOU AND THAT'S IT.
IN FACT OVER THE NEXT FEW DAYS
WE'RE STARTING A DRY STRETCH,
SUNNY STRETCH WITH JUST A FEW
DLOUDZ HERE AND THERE, THAT'S
MONDAY AND TUESDAY AND WEDNESDAY
AS WELL.
CURRENT TEMPERATURES ARE
SLIGHTLY ABOVE THAT FREEZING
MARK, WE'VE GOT A WIND CHILL,
THOUGH, FEELS LIKE OF ABOUT MINUS 2
TO MINUS 5 OUT THERE.
SLIGHT WIND CHILD AND YOU HAVE
TO DRESS FOR THAT IN THE
WE HAVE WIND GUSTS NEAR TO 40
KILOMETRES PER HOUR, A LITTLE
BIT STRONGER DOWN AT THE ISLAND
BECAUSE THE WIND IS PUSHING OVER
THE LAKE, LESS FRICTION, TO IT
TENDS TO BE STRONGER.
AS WE GO THROUGH THE DAY
TOMORROW, I MEANT TO PUT A PAUSE
IN THERE, BUT WE ARE LOOKING AT
GUSTY CONDITIONS TONIGHT AND
EASING THROUGH THE DAY TOMORROW.
NOT MUCH OF A WIND CHILL TO DEAL
WITH. JUST IN THE MORNING, FEELS
LIKE MINUS 6.
TOMORROW CLOSE TO SEASONAL
TEMPERATURES, THERE IS YOUR
SUNNY, DRY STRETCH.
WE HAVE GUSTY WINDS TUESDAY,
THAT'S COMING FROM THE SOUTHWEST
AND THAT IS A 14 THAT YOU ARE
SEEING.
THE AVERAGE -- SORRY, THE RECORD
HIGH FOR THAT DAY IS JUST OVER 18.
IT'S NOT RECORD BREAKING BUT
WE'LL BE INTO EVENING RAIN AND
FRIDAY IS THE DAY TO BRING THE