lots of Santa Claus parades going on.
Grey cup is going on and as you just
heard in sports it is snowing in Ottawa.
it's about two to five centimeters this
is a very small area of low pressure
that is sinking across southeastern
Ontario. the darker the blue the more
intense the snow and there into the most
intense part right now in Ottawa. it's
only going to taper off from this point
forward and again it's about two to four
maybe up to five centimeters of snow the
back end of it though is also bringing
some flurries across Lake Simcoe. some of
these flurries just starting to edge
down into northern York Region over the
next hour or two. So areas like
Whitchurch-Stouffville into possibly as far
south as Unionville, Markham and northern
Ajax and Whitby you may see a few
scattered flurries before this evening
is out. Otherwise we are not expecting
any accumulation. By the way future casts,
nothing. i got nothing. i got a little bit
of cloud to show you and that's it. in
fact over the next three days we are
starting a dry stretch. Fairly sunny
stretch with just a few clouds here and
there. that's gonna be Monday Tuesday and
Wednesday as well current temperatures
are just slightly above that freezing
mark. we've got a wind chill though feels
like of about minus 2 to minus 5 out there. so
yeah slight wind chill and you'll have
to dress for that in the morning. we've
got wind gusts right now very near to
40 km/h a little bit stronger down at the
island because the wind is pushing out
over the lake. less friction so it tends
to be a little bit stronger and as we go
through the day tomorrow. I meant to put
a pause in there and slow that down for
you but we are looking at gusty
conditions tonight. starting to ease
through the day tomorrow so we don't
have much of a windchill to deal with.
just in the morning it will feel like
about minus 6 tomorrow close to seasonal
temperatures. there is your sunny dry
stretch. we'll have gusty winds on
Tuesday that's coming in out of the
southwest and that is a 14 that you are
seeing. the average sorry the record high
for that day is just over 18. so it's not
gonna be record-breaking but will it be
into some evening rain Thursday and
Friday's the day you got to bring the
umbrella. this my friends the first
weekend of December. we'll start off with
a few showers bit end off fairly sunny.