Least stable.
Live AT QUEENS PARK, NOW BACK TO
YOU.
THANK YOU, PAUL.
DENISE ANDREACCHI IS IN FOR
ANWER TODAY.
WE LIKE THE TEMPERATURES TO GO
UP.
AND LIKE YOU SEE, CTV WEATHER
SKIRTING THE BRUCE PENINSULA,
AND RAINFALL IN THROUGH PARTS OF
COTTAGE COUNTRY, AND WEATHER
STATEMENT FOR TIMMINS, AND PARTS
OF NORTHEASTERN ONTARIO GETTING
IN FREEZING RAIN, IT'S ALL
ABOUT THE HIGH PRESSURE FOR THE
SOUTHERN TIER OF THE PROVINCE,
AND THE GTA.
PLUS A BEAUTIFUL SOUTHWEATERLY
FLOW OF AIR, GUSTY AT TIMES, AS
WE CAN SEE, AND ANYWHERE FROM 30
TO 50 KILOMETRES AN HOUR, ON AND
OFF THROUGHOUT THE MORNING AND
THE AFTERNOON, AND IT IS COMING
FROM THE SOUTHWEST, AND IT'S
DRAWING TEMPERATURES WAY UP.
YESTERDAY FOR THE GTA, AVERAGING
3 TO 4 degrees, AND CURRENTLY IN THE
HIGH SINGLE DIGITS ACROSS PARTS
OF THE SOUTHWEST, AND ALREADY AT
9 degrees IN HAMILTON, NIAGARA, AND
OAKVILLE.
WE DO HAVE THE RISK OF SOME
ACTIVE WEATHER.
AS WE CAN SEE, IT'S NORTH OF US,
AND IT'S VERY SLOW MOVING, AND T
OF The DAY TODAY, BASKING IN
NOVEMBER SUNSHINE, AND WELL
ABOVE THE SEASONAL AVERAGE WHERE
WE SHOULD BE.
PEARSON YESTEDAY, 3.5 DEGREES FOR AN
AVERAGE HIGH, AND BUMPING UP A
COUPLE MORE DEGREES IN THE NEXT
COUPLE OF HOURS, AND A MIX OF
SUN AND CLOUD.
WE WILL CONTINUE WITH THAT GUSTY
AIR.
WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO BE INDOORS
SHOPPING ON A DAY LIKE TODAY?
THESE ARE THE DAYS YOU NEED TO
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF, AND PARTLY
CLOUDY SKIES, AND TALKING ABOUT
THE WEEKEND WEATHER AND THE
LONG RANGE FORECAST COMING UP