all right thank you Paul. Denise
Andreacchi is in for a more line today.
we like temperatures to go up it was a
decent start to the day. yeah it
certainly is and lots of sunshine to come.
but as you can see behind me, we have
some active weather just skirting the
Bruce Peninsula. Some range fall in
through parts of cottage country and
even we have a special weather statement
for Timmins. So parts of northeastern
Ontario getting into some freezing rain.
It's all about the high pressure for the
southern tier of the province and the
JTA. plus we're getting a beautiful
southwesterly flow of air gusty at times
as we can see anywhere from about 30 to
50 km/h on and off throughout the
morning in the afternoon. but it's coming
from the southwest. so it's drawing
temperatures way up. yesterday for the
GTA, we averaged about 3 to 4
degrees. currently we're sitting in those
high single digits across parts of the
Southwest. We are already at 9 degrees at
Hamilton, Niagara and Oakville. We do have
the risk of some active weather. as we
can see it is north of us now but it's
very slow moving so most of the day
today we will be basking in some
November sunshine in through the east a
little bit cooler but still well above
the seasonal average where we should be.
Pearson yesterday 3.5
degrees for an average high. we're
already sitting at 9. we should bump
up a couple more degrees in the next
couple of hours and a mix of Sun and
clouds will continue with that gusty air.
but why would you want to be indoor
shopping on a day like today? These are
the type of days you need to take
advantage of. Partly cloudy skies for
most of the day and we're starting off
with a pretty good weekend we'll talk
more about the weekend weather in your
long range forecast coming up a little
later on, Ken.