mitchum owner picked up an assist on
carries 20th he is now the league leader
among rookies with 39 points Marner also
has a team high 12 multi point games
this season
Iran owes rookies have a hundred and
seventy five points so far this year
that is the most in the NHL welcome to
Sports Center everyone Kate alongside
Natasha
so unfortunate for the flames I mean
they looked like they had a little bit
of momentum as of late and now they just
looked like they're reeling once again
on the flip side though Toronto snapping
their mini slide and good for them to
pick up a monster win at home because we
know they're great on the road but they
have struggled at times of the Air
Canada center yeah they looks really
good on Monday and like you mentioned
Calgary all of a sudden really new 7 to
3 to the Oilers on Saturday and then get
shutout a game later so not much going
right for them lately with much more on
this one here is Glen Schuyler on the
panel thank you very much alongside Dave
Poole and Jeff O'Neal and Bob McKenzie
well much like his team what a
difference a year makes for Naz i'm
cadry remember that stretch last year at
the beginning one goal in 19 games just
snakebit now Jeff he's up to 20 goals
his shots finding the back of the net
yeah Glen he's really become a complete
player for the Toronto Maple Leafs he's
doing it at all ends of the rink all
different phases of the hockey game and
tonight soon as I give him props for
scoring in tight and not shooting from
outside the dots
he scores to wrist shot goals what a
season to have 20 in the bank right now
with a lot of hockey games left you know
the rest is just gravy glad there's no
reason why he can't get 3035 goals this
year for the Leafs meanwhile you don't
often see Johnny Hockey you get caught
with a body check but he took a licking
a couple of times this game the big one
of course Leo Komarov running him over
the flames wanted a head shot Bob how do
you think the league will review this
well my esteemed panel colleague here
Jeff O'Neill said right away as soon as
it happened that was a clean but violent
hit and I'd be very surprised if the
league saw it any other way than that it
was not late it was not a charge it was
not an elbow there was no launching
involved now was there contact to the
head absolutely there was but I believe
the league would say this is unavoidable
contact if they had a taller player and
a smaller player there was body on body
contact the head contact was incidental
and while it was a very violent hit and
look for a moment as it Johnny Gaudreau
might be under the hockey game and the
fact he came back was a real positive I
don't believe there would be any
supplementary discipline and as we
pointed out during the game no penalty
call on the place so the refs appear to
have gotten right and I suspect the
league will endorse that called non call
by the referees