tomorrow on the social the actor known
for starring in huge hits like The OC
and now Cardinal Billy Campbell alright
make sure you're engaging with us right
now in real time online we want to share
her some news but every time there's
something happen your company that were
really excited and proud of we do love
to share it with all of you and our
president of broadcasting and content
for bel media's name is Randy Lenox he
is an absolute legend in the music
industry he's going to be honored for
his extensive contributions to Canada's
music scene because it was just
announced a little earlier today he'll
be presented with the wall creoles
special achievement award happening at
Juno week and a huge gala we want to
send you a huge congratulations Juno
Awards happen Sunday April 2nd you can
watch it right here on CTV and we will
keep you posted as more information
about the show is released big question
that a lot of people are pondering this
weekend as well should real live animals
appear in film and television or is
computer-generated imagery or CGI the
better option according to TMZ animal
rights activists animal rights activists
that is will be picketing movie theaters
over the film a dogs purpose recently a
video surfaced of what appears to be a
frightened German Shepherd being forced
into a pool of rushing water during the
filming of the movie the production
company told TMZ that they did not force
the dog to go through with the stunt
instead they called a break and filmed
it once the dog calmed down and was ok
with it so this is a big controversy
because it's affecting the film now as
the actress on the panel what's your
take on this it's interesting the CGI
option because I shot a film last summer
and we had to we had to sing with a bear
I was supposed to scare us and the
director met with various trainers and
in the end he he didn't trust them quite
enough so basically it was CGI but I
feel like sometimes it is true that on
set there's that feeling of because
we're filming fiction we can push the
limits and it's it's as if we weren't
shooting reality
and me as a child actor I mean we're
talking about animals right now but to
me it's the same thing with child actors
I've seen and I've experienced moments
[Applause]