third period about to get underway here
at the MTS Center in a 2-1 game for the
Anaheim Ducks no scoring in period
number two and rooftop finds Elaine and
blows one by Jonathan Bernier jets have
the one nothing lead path left to save
out the Fowler woven Shaw beds in the
that was a short-handed tally and then
gets loud theez the attack it ends up
Raquelle who finds some room on the
short side and that's the way we stand
going into the third period that a third
carriage starts for the Winnipeg Jets
with a power play I had a little bit of
a mix-up there at the end of period
number two right now they have Kessler's
number on the board is tesslar perry in
the box for the ducks and bart safely
for the Winnipeg Jets yeah probably
for each fairies penalty because they'll
saw Kessler strikes and even the
original combatants and then as you
mentioned it was quarry Lake wheeler
so the Jets do have the power play
fourth power play tonight for the one a
peg just as they're down by one Fowler
and you'll dig it free cleared to the
line kept in knocked down by Blake
Wheeler for Dustin Byfuglien into the
swat-bot
a little shot and can't Fowler got in
front of us ducks so good at getting
sticks and passing and shooting lanes
get slapped couldn't handle it and
wanted his out of Lowry for Blake
wheeler wheeler put it to the front of
the net Nolan could get a stick on it
after it is Nick patan four out of Lowry
back for patan
ducks very impressive on the penalty
kill cleaner back up top four puffs of
the Rashad Bernier the same
away patan back for Byfuglien buckling
into the swabbing for little Getzlaf
tucked it away
the tan sends it down low Bieksa with
little after him Lowry helps so Lowry is
up with it for a wheeler in front trying
to go back side that got tipped away and
it will slip out the center ice began
very crispy back in for Lake wheeler
wheeler takes a bump leaves it for
Buckland around for Andrew cop 35
seconds in the powered by cops couldn't
handle it